yourmusic.com 2010-06-28

# Yourmusic.com

Privacy Policy

This Web site, located at yourmusic.com (this "Site") is operated by yourmusic.com, a subscription music service owned by Direct Brands, Inc. (referred to collectively herein, along with its affiliates, as "yourmusic.com" or "we" or "us" or "our"). 

_Your privacy is important._

At yourmusic.com, we know that your privacy is important to you. It's important to us, too. That's why we want you to know about the personal information we collect, how we use that information and with whom it may be shared, in connection with your use of this Site. 

You're always in control:  
Except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, the only information that we collect from you is information that you give us when you register and when you make purchases or otherwise use this Site. We use that information, for example, to service your account and to personalize your experience at this Site. Other than as set forth in this Privacy Policy and/or in the Terms and Conditions, we'll never share your e-mail address with third parties interested in e-mailing you, or send you our own promotional e-mails, without your consent (either communicated to us or to a company that we have since acquired), except in connection with your transactions on this site. However, if you became a yourmusic.com subscriber after June 1, 2006 (or if you were a yourmusic.com subscriber before that date but have since opted-in to this Privacy Policy) we may send you promotional messages without your consent, but you may opt-out by visiting Subscription Preferences at yourmusic.com and changing your e-mail preferences. 

To see (or change) your current subscriber information in your user account, click "Your Account." (You will need to do this for each account, if you have more than one account.) If you wish to change information offline, or if there are circumstances in which you wish to have your spouse, relative, or other trusted friend have access to your information, please write to us at yourmusic.com, PO Box 91601, Rantoul IL 61866-8601. 

**For information about how you can change your preferences regarding the use and disclosure of your contact information for marketing purposes, see the Your Opt-Out Rights section below.**

Here's the information we gather:   
When you register at this Site, we ask for certain basic information to service your account: for example, name, shipping and billing addresses, e-mail address, phone number, credit card or PayPal account and other payment information. We may also collect certain demographic information such as your music preferences, age, gender, geographical location, language, time zone, income and education. (Some of the information we ask for may be optional.) 

We may also ask you to indicate your Listening Preferences. This enables us to customize your shopping experience when you come to this Site. You may change your Listening Preferences at any time. To change your current Listening Preference, click "Subscription Preferences." 

You may have the option to use certain services, such as Tell A Friend, which may require you to provide us with transmittal information for your friends or family. 

Naturally, we also pay attention to what you buy, we keep track of your shopping, purchases, traffic patterns, the pages you visit, and related site usage inside our website. This helps us to understand your musical tastes more fully and to present you with better recommendations, more relevant offers, important news about artists and other announcements we think may interest you. 

We may conduct some or all of these activities through our third party service providers, who provide these services on our behalf. 

Your credit card information:   
We'll keep your credit card information on file, but we have designed our site not to display the entire credit card information. Plus, you can always choose to change to a new card or delete one of your credit cards entirely from our files. To see (or change) your current credit card status, click "Billing/Preferences" in "Your Account." 

When you sign up for a subscription you authorize yourmusic.com to place a temporary, $1 authorization charge on your card. This temporary charge _will not_ be converted into an actual charge to you; it is used only to verify your billing address and the validity of your card. The temporary charge will reduce the amount available on your card by $1 for a short period of time. 

Why your transactions are secure:   
We use industry standard encryption technology to safeguard your credit card or PayPal account information. The technology used is SSL (Secure Socket Layer), which is supported by all web browsers that are version 4.0 or newer. Your credit card or PayPal account information is encrypted as it travels over the Internet using encryption strengths that are standard in the industry. Upon our receipt, it is stored on restricted-access computers located at restricted-access sites. Notwithstanding this, due to the open nature of the Internet, we cannot guarantee that any information stored on our servers, or transmitted to or from a user, will be free from unauthorized access. Please be careful whenever sending personal information to us via the "Contact Customer Service" feature on this Site or by e-mail. For example, do not send us your account password or credit card or PayPal account information via these methods, as they may not be a secure means of transferring information. By using this Site, you acknowledge that you understand and agree to assume these risks. 

Our employees with access to your personal information are trained to follow specific practices concerning its proper handling. 

We have designed this Site not to display your full credit card or PayPal account information. Your account is password-protected. You must use your password to submit an order or view your personal information in your account. This Site is designed to sign you out automatically if your session remains inactive for more than 20 minutes. If you share a computer, we recommend that you always sign out before leaving it unattended. 

In the unlikely event that we believe that the security of your personal information in our possession or control may have been compromised, we may seek to notify you of that development. If a notification is appropriate, we would endeavor to do so as promptly as possible under the circumstances, and, to the extent we have your e-mail address, we may notify you by e-mail. 

Technical Information:  
When you visit this Site, we may collect technical information that does not, by itself, identify a specific individual. This information may include, for example, the address (or "URL") of the website that you came from before visiting this Site, which pages you visit on this Site, which computer platform, monitor, web browser and related software and settings you used to view this Site and any search terms you have entered on this Site or a referral site. This technical data is aggregated and used to measure and improve the effectiveness of this Site. We may collect your IP (Internet Protocol) address and/or domain name to help diagnose problems with our server, administer our site, see where our site traffic is coming from and identify our users. We may also collect other information via this Site, such as site usage activity and preferences, also known as demographic or profile data. We may combine these types of technical data with your personal information. We may conduct some or all of these activities through our third party service providers, who provide these services on our behalf. 

We may use "cookies" (described in more detail below) and clear GIFs in this Site or in our communications with you to enhance the functionality of this Site and to make your transactions and other activities more customized, convenient and efficient. We may use cookies, for example, to remember user preferences, to minimize the need for you to re-enter information, and to store information about your activities on this Site and other technical information. Cookies and/or clear GIFs may be placed by our third party service providers, who provide these services on our behalf. 

What you should know about cookies:  
Cookies are small pieces of information that we may send through your browser or other software to your hard drive. A cookie lets us recognize you and provide a more meaningful and personalized shopping experience when you come back to our site. 

Most web browsers are set to accept cookies automatically, but you can change this setting. However, you may need to leave your cookies "on" in order to take full advantage of the features of this Site. If your cookies are "off," see your browser's "help topics" to learn how to change the setting. Additionally, in the event that we use Flash cookies, your Flash player can be set to accept, reject or delete them. 

With whom is information shared?  
We may release specific personal information for the following reasons: We may use outside companies to host and maintain this Site, to provide you with certain merchandise you purchase, to provide some of the services you use on our sites as well as for managing some of our internal operations such as data analysis and e-mails. As a result, these companies do have access to specific information necessary to perform these services, but we require them to keep this information confidential and not to use it for any other reason. We will release your personal information to the proper persons when we believe, in good faith, that we are required to comply with a law or legal process, cooperate with or participate in legal investigations, enforce our user agreements or protect the rights, property or safety of yourmusic.com or other persons or entities. 

Aggregate statistics:  
From time to time we provide aggregate statistics about our customers, site traffic, sales and other site-related information to reputable companies. Of course, if you have registered in an outside customer reward program in which yourmusic.com is a participating merchant, we will provide your reward program with the necessary information about your purchases so that you can be awarded your points or other rewards. 

**Your Opt-Out Rights:**

E-mail addresses:  
We never sell or rent your name and e-mail address to other online marketers of products or services without your consent. You make the decisions on how you would like to hear from us (in addition to the monthly e-mails and transactional e-mails that are part of your subscription) and if you are interested in receiving valuable offers from other reputable marketers of products and services. You can change your preferences at any time by going to the "Subscription Preferences" section of this Site. In addition, all promotional e-mail that you receive from yourmusic.com (not including service e-mails, such as the monthly e-mails that are part of your subscription) will always allow you to unsubscribe to future e-mail promotions from yourmusic.com if you decide to do so at a later date. 

Postal mailing lists:  
We make our postal mailing list available to selected companies whose products and services we think you will enjoy. Once again, you have the option of removing your name and address from our mailing list by simply writing to us at yourmusic.com, PO Box 91601, Rantoul IL 61866-8601. Or you can go to the Customer Service section of this Site and send us an e-mail requesting we remove your name from our mailing list. Please do not forget to include your account number (but not your password or any other sensitive information!). 

External sites:  
yourmusic.com may run sweepstakes with select companies or place advertisements or other promotional offers from select companies on our website or in our e-mails. When you choose to participate in these sweepstakes or promotional offers, you may link to these businesses' websites and be asked to give them personal information, or we may send over your personal information if you enter it on this Site. These businesses operate independently from yourmusic.com. Any personal information that is given to them is at your option and is no longer controlled by us or our Privacy Policy. 

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf. These companies may employ cookies and action tags (also known as "single pixel gifs" or "web beacons") to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and action tags in generally not personally identifiable (unless, for example, you provide personally identifiable information to them through an ad or e-mail message). We encourage you to read these businesses' privacy policies if you should have any concerns about how they will care for your personal information. 

Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA): 

This Site is a website directed to the general public. We do not knowingly collect information from children under 13. 

Consent: By using this Site and providing us with your personal information, you are accepting the privacy practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of such updates by posting the updated policy on this Site, and, depending on the nature of the change, we may also notify you by e-mail. Please check back here occasionally. You will always find the latest version posted here. 

Please note that because a customer information database is customarily considered a business asset, yourmusic.com shall have the right to transfer it in a merger, sale of some or all of its company, consolidation, change in control, reorganization, liquidation or in an action for bankruptcy. 

Comments: If you have any questions or comments about our Privacy Policy, please send us an e-mail by clicking on Contact Customer Service. 

Date of Last Update to Privacy Policy: 11/21/2008
